Or?
-Yes.
Then you get to know, in several years.
Crafts, carpenter or mason.
Is it the dream profession
Yes I think so.
-Not blacksmith, or anything?
Yes, it would have been fun.
Imagine forging full time, to feed on it.
It would have been fun.
Or type ... -... Youtuber?
Or small farmer.
Get some cows and grow a little bit of everything possible, sold a little.
If there was an economy in such things, I would have easily tinkering with it.
After I have taken the dishes and removed a little neighbor.
I'll take and clean our hall.
This is what it looks like right now.
I will ... maybe not today when I have to screw, do not want to risk the children wake up now at 21.
We have this one that we have put together, with boxes.
They are already smoking.
Should clear from winter stuff, hats.
Put down swimwear, bathing rings and all that it may be.
Sun creams.
Clean through this cabinet.
We have bought new boxes.
When I ordered these I ordered the wrong boxes, or we got wrong, I don't know.
Probably it was me who ordered wrong.
Oh, my poor flowers.
We have a box in front of the basement, where I thought to put those tall flowers.
And they a little lower.
Then of course I bought Rosenskär, although I found yellow.
I think whites are by far the finest, but the yellow ones were also fine.
I bought them for another pot.
The idea is that this will be a big bush sometime, an oxygen hydrangea.
It should be huge and bushy I had thought.
Around the entrance here, but it didn't turn out so well.
It's not going so fast.
Don't know if I said it in the last vlog, but the goats cooked up our plants.
And the hens sand baths so that the soil disappears.
Should you get it tidy and nice now
New lane.
You have shit down so damn.
We have had problems with chicken mites.
But we bought some type of killer malway.
I don't know what it is called, but a mite that eats up such mites.
You buy them in a pipe, release them in the chicken house, they eat up these mites
And when the food ends, ie the mite, they also die.
Or they die when it gets too cold.
So then they also disappear, finally.
She refuses to leave
Selma: Klara, finished, go
Selma: I will win
Selma: Yeah, I won
Svea: I won Selma: Nah !!
Are you drunk
I might have this to you then, because I have just done wrong
Oskar: Maybe it's just as good.
I have built together and Oskar redesigns.
I just told Oskar that the top of the most boring thing is to go to the dump, order.
Throw glass and metal.
But this fuck everything, build something together, make mistakes and can rebuild it again.
Have you lay down in there again!
Little hen.
She has been in the box again.
Ah
Thought I would do a little thing to the hens now that it is so hot outside.
One thing that can make them cool off a bit was actually one of you who wrote and advised me about this.
You should have a swap.
Maize.
And water.
You freeze it, the ice block puts with corn in when it is hot outside
Then they get some cold water.
A little ice cream.